[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "That psychologically he got the glory straight off the top and actually hasn't reached those heights again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "As they say it's all gone downhill from there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "What do you make overall of the gymnastics for the ladies been in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Historic day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "How do you see the Americans over all when it gets to track and field?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think the Americans will do well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "If you can't trust a foot race, what can you trust?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "How important is it to America to reassume the ascendancy over the Chinese after the Chinese went ahead in Beijing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I think it's very important, I'm not sure it's going to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Beijing"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, actually my memories of my Olympic experience, Piers, are quite good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "When you see all the attention that she is attracting for her phenomenal performance, what do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I think it's very unfortunate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Do you think that the only way to really eradicate it from sport, from the Olympics, is to make the punishment so severe that other athletes just wouldn't contemplate it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "It was going to be on prime time, it's probably the biggest coverage that USA track and field are going to receive for a lot of time, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["USA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How can it be an advantage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I disagree with Michael in a few -- in a few points of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "But what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, I think that the wording in all of this is just very important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "So what's your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I love it, I love her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "I'd imagine it was very competitive when you were young, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Absolutely, yes, and a lot of us, and so I learned to be competitive from a very young age.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "And you also used to run barefoot, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Did you beat the boys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "You are really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "You were brought up around here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "How far from this very spot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "I would say about five minutes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Evander, I mean, over the years have you learned to possibly accept that he nicked that first one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "He could have, but I got the second one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Is that how we're leaving this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", ":", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "What do you think, Lennox?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "EWIS: I think that's -- winning the Olympics is a great thing to do because you're basically, you start as an amateur boxer and to complete your amateur tutelage, you have to be an Olympic gold medallist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lennox"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Evander, do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, I do -- I do believe that, you know, (INAUDIBLE) the Olympics and is -- you know, just like graduated with a degree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Who was top dog?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It all depends on how you look at it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Who would be the boxer in history heavyweight you would least want to fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "You know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "He is the first heavyweight for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Who were your personal heroes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Well, Ali was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Those eyes bearing down on you followed by fists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Did you ever get people coming up, trying it out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "How is your ear?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "It's good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Did it nearly actually fall off in the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, you know, he snagged a piece of it, and it kind of went out in a (INAUDIBLE) and spit it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Well, that moment when you realize Mike Tyson has decided to eat your ear in the middle of a fight, what goes through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Shocking.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Well, Lennox, when you were watching that, what did you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I was horrified.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lennox"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "He did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "So we're both sitting here, we've both been bitten.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "But I did knock you out, didn't I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "RP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Those Americans wanted you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What do you think of your country at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Of course, I think when it all come down, people are divided.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What do you think of the place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I think it's a great place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "CC", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "What would be the best advice to young Olympians that you would give?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Me, all I would really say, you know, we create our own pressure, so if you feel pressure, you know, you're creating it, and one thing I would say that, you know, nobody really remembers any other medal but gold, so have gold in your mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "By all means say you did well to get a bronze and silver, but everyone here wants to win gold, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "It's about winning, isn't it, Evander?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Yes, it's about winning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "So my final question, is if it all suddenly kicked off right now here, you know, something happened, one of you said something, and you got it on again, who would win the third battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "JJ", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I would, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Evander?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Of course he would say that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "What do you recall, if anything, of what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Piers, what I remember most about that day, as you guys know, we play football, we go on the routine, you know, get changed, and then get ready, you go out and you do the warm-up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday", "Monday"]}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "What happened to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "I mean, it happened on a Saturday but I didn't wake up until the Monday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Since what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "Since the incident happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dubai"]}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "When did you play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "I was in Dubai.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May"]}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "When was this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "In May.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "And how did it feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "It feel very good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 710, "question": "And you would have been on the Great Britain soccer team, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 711, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Great Britain"]}}]